<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>LibreNMS Notifications</title>
 <description>RSS feed for notifications to LibreNMS users</description>
 <link>https://www.librenms.org/</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2016 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 <ttl>1800</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Hello World!</title>
  <description>This is the first notification. We will post these whenever an upcoming major change is about to happen.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Cisco syslog parsing changes</title>
  <description>We have overhauled the Cisco syslog parsing.  Please monitor your syslog entries from Cisco IOS, IOSXR, and CatOS devices.  If you notice any issues please open a new issue on GitHub and include the original syslog message.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
   <title>Billing Data Changes</title>
   <description>We have updated the method for storing billing data, removing a lot of information stored in
   the database which was not used.  Please check that your billing data is updating as expected, and
   if you notice any problems open an issue on GitHub.</description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
   <title>Introduction of default purge interval or alert history</title>
   <description>We have introduced a purge setting for alert history which is set to 365 days as default. If you would like to update this then please
   set $config['alert_log_purge'] to a custom value (set in days).</description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
   <title>The Alerts Menu has moved</title>
   <description>The Alerts menu has been relocated to a top level menu on the far right.  To make room for this, Plugins have been moved
   to the overview menu.</description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
   <title>Wireless Section in Beta</title>
   <description>The new wireless section is under development. Please visit our community to discuss these changes and help improve LibreNMS.
   https://t.libren.ms/5fglp</description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 1 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
   <title>Update to alerting to normal users</title>
   <description>We have released an update to fix normal users receiving alerts with no ability to turn this off. An option is now available within the General alert settings section to
   enable this. Please note that the default is off to match with the other default contact settings. If you expect normal users to receive alerts then you should enable this new option.</description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
  <item>
    <title>Legacy Alert Templates and Transports removed</title>
    <description>As described previously, Legacy Alert Templates and Transports have been removed.  You can find more info here: https://community.librenms.org/t/deprecation-notice-alerting-legacy-transports-and-templates/5915</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cisco Temperature Sensor Threshold Values Stored as High Limits</title>
    <description>During discovery, some temperature sensors discovered on Cisco devices had their highest temperature value stored as warning high limit. For new discovered devices, this value is now stored as high limit.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
   <item>
    <title>LibreNMS Python Dispatcher Service V2 (breaking change)</title>
    <description>Version two of the LibreNMS python dispatcher service is merged. This code now requires Redis 5.x and redis-py 3.x to operate (if using distributed polling). If you are using the dispatcher service with Redis and have not updated, polling will stop functioning.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>RutOS 2xx pinState renamed</title>
    <description>RutOS 2xx pinState renamed to rutos2xx_pinState.  Update any alert rules you may have.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cisco Wireless Controller classified as Wireless</title>
    <description>Cisco WLC is now classified as type "Wireless" instead of "Network".  Update any alert rules you may have.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
